# **Thomas Jackson**

E-mail: Tom.Jackson1711@gmail.com

Phone: +44 (0) 7494092928

**Graphics & Games Programmer** Portfolio: <a href="https://tomizzed2001.github.io">https://tomizzed2001.github.io</a>

Vulkan

OpenGL

A confident and dedicated individual with a wide range of communication, technical, and critical thinking skills. Excels in teamwork both as a leader and team member to provide valuable contributions to the task at hand. A logical minded, creative programmer who puts to use a combination of learnt knowledge and experience to efficiently produce quality work.

#### **Technical Skills**

**Programming Languages Development Tools Graphics APIs** Experienced In

C/C++

C#

**GLSL** 

Python

Java

Unreal 5 /4

Unity

RenderDoc

Git

**Physics** 

Rendering

**Mesh Optimisation** 

**Engine Development** 

Animation

# **Employment History**

### CLO Coffee - Roastery & Café

Leeds, UK

Café Operator Jul 2023 – Mar 2024

Organising a small team of people to efficiently operate the café.

Solving customer complaints and or queries in a timely manner.

Communicating with café management to ensure stock levels were maintained.

**Nandos** Leeds / York, UK Front of House Staff Jun 2019 - May 2023

Greeting and interacting with customers during their dining experience.

Working as part of a team to assure customer satisfaction.

Managing time effectively to maximise customer turnover during busy periods.

## **Education**

**University of Leeds** Leeds, UK

MSc in High Performance Graphics & Games Engineering

Distinction

Relevant Modules: Animation and Simulation, Geometric Processing, Rendering, High Performance Graphics,

Dissertation: Marching Cubes for Low-Poly Mesh Generation

Awards: MSc High-performance graphics and games Engineering prize, for achieving

the highest degree classification on the course.

York, UK

Sep 2020 - Jun 2023

Sep 2023 - Sep 2024

### **University of York**

BEng in Computer Science

First Class Honours

Relevant Modules: Object-Oriented Programming, Software Engineering, High Performance Computing

Dissertation: Washed Up: A 2D Survival and Tower Defence Game in Unity

**Garforth Academy** Leeds, UK Sep 2018 - Jun 2020 A-Level Mathematics - Grade A

A-Level Physics - Grade A

A-Level Computer Science - Grade A

## **Hobbies & Interests**

During my free time I enjoy creating my own games and playing the latest PC games, especially the survival ones! I also love to participate in Esports events, having represented York University during my time there, both as a player and an organiser; it's something I really like to keep up with. Away from my computer, I'm passionate about exploring the British countryside and often go walking and cycling on scenic routes. When opportunity arises, I'm also a hobbyist fossil hunter on the Yorkshire Coast and love showing off my collection.